tapesh.com 2006-06-16

# Tapesh.Com - Privacy Policy

**  
Tapesh.Com Privacy Policy **  
*Tapesh.Com takes your privacy very seriously.   
Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy

. **What This Privacy Policy Covers**

  * This policy covers how Tapesh.Com treats personal information that we collect and receive. Personal information is information about you that is personally identifiable like your name, address, email address, or phone number, and that is not otherwise publicly available. 
  * This policy does not apply to the practices of companies or sites that Tapesh.Com does not own or control, or to people that Tapesh.Com does not employ or manage.

**Information Collection and Use**

**General**

  * Tapesh.Com collects personal information when you register with our services that require registration, when you visit pages or the pages of certain Tapesh.Com partners, and when you join any programs. 
  * When you register we ask for information such as your name, email address, birth date, gender, zip code, occupation, industry, and personal interests. Once you register with Tapesh.Com services of any kind and sign in to our services, you are not anonymous to us. 
  * Tapesh.Com automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address , cookies information, and the page you request. 
  * Tapesh.Com uses information for the following general purposes: to customize the advertising and content you see, fulfill your requests for products and services, improve our services, contact you, conduct research, and provide anonymous reporting for internal and external clients. 

**Information Sharing and Disclosure**

  * Tapesh.Com does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or nonaffiliated companies except to provide products or services you've requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances: 
    * We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims; 
    * We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of Tapesh.Com terms of use, or as otherwise required by law. 
    * We transfer information about you if Tapesh.Com is acquired by or merged with another company.
  * Tapesh.Com displays targeted advertisements based on personal information, and site content. Advertisers (including ad serving companies) may assume that people who interact with, view, or click on targeted ads meet the targeting criteria - for example, female visitors from a particular geographic area. 
    * Tapesh.Com does not provide any personal information to the advertiser when you interact with or view a targeted ad. However, by interacting with or viewing an ad you are consenting to the possibility that the advertiser will make the assumption that you meet the targeting criteria used to display the ad. 
    * Tapesh.Com advertisers include financial service providers (such as banks, insurance agents, stock brokers and mortgage lenders) and non-financial companies (such as stores, airlines, and software companies, entertainment sites). 

**Cookies**

  * Tapesh.Com may set and access tapesh cookies on your computer. 
  * Tapesh.Com may let other companies that show advertisements on some of our pages to set and access their cookies on your computer. Other companies' use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not this one. Advertisers or other companies do not have access to Tapesh.Com's cookies.. 

**Your Ability to Edit and Delete Your Account Information and Preferences**

**General**

  * You can edit any of your Tapesh Accounts Information at any time. 
  * We reserve the right to send you certain communications relating to the Tapesh.Com service, such as service announcements, administrative messages and the Tapesh.Com Newsletter. 
  * You can delete your accounts either on your own, or by asking us to do it for you. 

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

  * Tapesh.Com may update this policy, therefore it is your responsiblity to check here time to time to keep yourself updated with our policy. 

**Questions and Suggestions**

  * If you have questions or suggestions, please use our contact page, or you can contact us at: webmaster@tapesh.com 

Tapesh.Com Entertainment   
Scottsdale, AZ - USA   
(480) 221-4606
